http://tylermuseum.org/about/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
The Tyler Museum of Art is committed to respecting the privacy of its online guests, customers, members, donors, and friends.
This Privacy Policy governs personal information provided or obtained on Tylermusem.org. It also explains how we may collect, use, and sometimes share that information.
Provided Information
The TMA collects the information you voluntarily provide in communications and transactions with the Museum, such as your name, phone number, email address, credit card information, and any digital images or written content you upload.
We use this information only for ordinary Museum purposes, such as to respond to your inquiries, update your Friends or member profile, process transactions, and for posting of information on a Museum Site as requested by you. With your permission, we may also send you Museum-related news and information. You may opt out of Museum communications at any time.
Transactional Information
Information you provide is collected in connection with transactions, such as donations to the Museum, memberships, fundraisers, or purchases. This information includes your payment card information, billing address, phone number, and email address. We honor requests that donations be anonymous to the public, subject to any reporting obligations mandated by law.
Your payment card information will not be used for any purpose other than to process your transaction. Other personal information may be used to update the Museum’s records of donors and customers.
Children’s Privacy
The Tyler Museum of Art is concerned about protecting children's privacy. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. The Tyler Museum of Art encourages all parents to participate in their children’s exploration of the Internet and to teach them about protecting their personal information while online. We urge those concerned or with questions to contact us for more information.
Contact Us
Your questions, comments and feedback are very important to us. For privacy-related issues, please contact the Executive Director of the Tyler Museum of Art by phone on 903-595-1001, by email to director@tylermuseum.org or by post addressed c/o Executvie Director, Tyler Museum of Art, 1300 South Mahon, Tyler, TX 75701.
© 2017 Tyler Museum of Art Proudly Designed and Hosted By:
No more posts to load.
Load More Posts
Loading posts...
